(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
KOBO KANAERU
Special guests are here to join the fun so don't blink
KUREIJI OLLIE / AYUNDA RISU / AIRANI IOFITTEEN / PAVOLIA REINE
VESTIA ZETA
SHIRAKAMI FUBUKI / SAKURA MIKO / MOCOCO ABYSSGARD / FUWAWA ABYSSGARD
OURO KRONII
NATSUIRO MATSURI / OOZORA SUBARU
OTONOSE KANADE / TODOROKI HAJIME
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
HOUSHOU MARINE
The moment we've all been waiting for...
5... 4... 3... 2... 1...
Ha-a-ha-a-a...
こんなことなるなんて　会う前にわかってたら
If I'd known it would turn out like this before we met...
もう少しだけ　しゃんとした僕を　見せられたはずなんだ
I should have been able to show you a slightly more proper version of myself.
どうしたらいいのかなんて　頭ではわかってるけど
I know in my head what I should do, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
With just a casual word or two...
嬉し顔が出ちゃって　こんなバレバレじゃ格好悪いな
A happy face slips out; it's so obvious, it's embarrassing.
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな　今も顔が照れくさくて
But I can't just back down like this, even now my face is blushing.
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです　この気持ち伝わったら
I can't say that I love you; if these feelings got through...
嬉しいだって怖いから　何も言えずまたさよなら
Because I'm happy but also scared, I say goodbye again without saying a word.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです　明日こそは言えるかな
I love you so much I can't help it; I wonder if I'll be able to say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕に同じように　恋してたらなんて考えちゃうな
I can't help but think, what if you were in love with me too?
会えない日が続いてる　このままじゃよろしくない
The days we can't meet continue; this isn't good.
会ったところで何ができるってわけじゃないんだけど
It's not like I can do much even if we did meet, but...
こんな恋は二度とないな　頭ではわかってるけど
A love like this will never happen again; I know it in my head, but...
眩しすぎるその笑顔が
That smile of yours is too dazzling.
僕を焦らせるんだ　ずっと見ていたくなるような
It makes me feel impatient; I want to keep looking at it forever.
見逃したくなくなってしまうような　こんな気持ちわかるのかな
Like I don't want to miss a thing; I wonder if you understand these feelings.
あなたが笑ってるなら　それでいいんです　でも隣は僕がいいな
If you're laughing, that's enough for me; but I wish I was the one beside you.
もしかしたら実は　ずっと気づいてるんじゃないかな
Maybe you've actually known all along.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't help it.
言えるかな
Can I say it?
全てをひっくり返すくらいの一番なセリフは
The best line that would turn everything upside down
言えそうにないや
Doesn't seem like I can say it
どうしてもこの気持ちは
No matter what, this feeling
抑えられそうにはないんだ
Doesn't seem like it can be suppressed
あなたと出会ったあの日から
From that day I met you
ずっと気持ちは変わらないけど
My feelings haven't changed, but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say I like you
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you
足掻いたって空回り
Struggling, I just go in circles
何も言えずまたさよなら
Can't say anything, so goodbye again
あなたのことが好きすぎて堪らないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to say it tomorrow for sure
あなたも僕と同じように
If you, just like me,
恋してたらなんて考えてる
Were in love, I'm thinking...
でも分かってる
But I know
考えすぎってこと
That I'm overthinking it
Kobo Kanaeru at your service. Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hi everyone! Konbanwa!
Hi everyone! Good evening!
こぼ・かなえるです！
I'm Kobo Kanaeru!
こぼの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream 2025! Pachi pachi pachi!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D birthday stream 2025! Clap clap clap!
How was Kobo's performance? Hmm? Hmm?
どうだった？
How was it?
またギターで出てきたよね？えへ！
I came out with a guitar again, right? Hehe!
えーっとちょっと待って。
Um, wait a second.
Let me put the guitar down first.
よしよしよしよし。んしょ。
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho. There we go.
Okay! Fuu! Hai!
Okay! Phew! Alright!
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream 2025!
こぼの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an...
アイドルみたいコンサート、テーマ3D生誕配信...
idol-like concert themed 3D birthday stream...
...for about an hour
with a lot of amazing and awesome guests. I bet you guys can't wait!
Hey Kobo, おいしそう、ちょっと違... あー！
Hey Kobo, looking tasty, wait that's different... Ah!
Chat nice, nice eyes chat. You noticed it!
Yeah, you're right. Look at Kobo's new stage! Wah!
でかい！
It's huge!
新しいステージだよ！
It's a new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here.
チルス、大きなチルス。
Cilus, a big Cilus.
おにゅおにゅおにゅおにゅ... えへへ！
Onyu onyu onyu onyu... ehehe!
And so many stars! Stars! So many stars!
And then a big, a big rainbow right here! Big, very big rainbow!
And so many clouds because... mmm... I don't know, I think it's just very aesthetic.
Yeah, and the floor! Floor!
フロア見て、わあ！なんかパターン...
Look at the floor, wow! Some kind of pattern...
海みたい。
It's like the sea.
You know? Yeah, like my hair. Hehe.
So, um, don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay?
Especially later, okay? Get a lot of screenshots! Okay?
And then post your comments, your moments, your impressions, everything with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS.
そして、こぼの3Dバースデー配信、SNSにハッシュタグ #3DKobornDay2025 をつけて...
And post about Kobo's 3D birthday stream on SNS with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025...
コメントや思い出、感想などなど投稿してね！
And post your comments, memories, impressions, and so on!
Right, are you guys ready for the next performance? Hmm hmm hmm?
Okay, let's go to the next performance! Mmm... wait, I try to remember...
Okay, let's go to the next performance! Mmm... wait, I'm trying to remember...
...my last position, this position.
Ah, okay.
覚えてます！
I remember!
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？
Now everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべっちゅして
Give me a special kiss
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby I love you is not enough
一番大違い
The biggest difference
君が作るオリジナルの
The original one you make
とくべっちゅして
Give me a special kiss
眩しくて目が覚めて (Oh yeah)
So bright that I woke up (Oh yeah)
愛しく想ってる (Oh yeah)
I'm thinking of you dearly (Oh yeah)
眠り姫のように
Like Sleeping Beauty
優しく口づけて
Kiss me gently
夢見たこの世界 (Oh yeah)
This world I dreamed of (Oh yeah)
夕焼け色、君がいる (Oh yeah)
In the sunset color, you are there (Oh yeah)
全てに触れずに
Without touching everything
二人だけでいよう
Let's be just the two of us
私のこと苦戦して
Struggle over me
君だけのものになってもいい
It's okay to become yours alone
なんでもある日の
On a day where everything exists
なんでもないキスしてね
Give me an ordinary kiss, okay?
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby I love you is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっと give me a kiss more 私は
Hey, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
...full of you
ほどけないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot
小指キュって縛って
Tie my pinky tightly
そうよ一生一緒がいいの
That's right, I want us to be together forever
特別中が欲しい
I want a special kiss
二人きり週末は (Oh yeah)
On weekends just the two of us (Oh yeah)
奏でてよハーモニー (Oh yeah)
Play the harmony (Oh yeah)
流れ星見たら
If you see a shooting star
私を想ってほしい
I want you to think of me
甘々な君なのに (Oh yeah)
Even though you're so sweet (Oh yeah)
広い街吸い込まれ (Oh yeah)
Being sucked into the wide city (Oh yeah)
戦う姿に
To your fighting figure
大きな花丸だね
A big perfect score mark
好きなところ 優しいところ
Things I like, your kind side
嫌いなところも 優しいところ
Even things I hate, are your kind side
誰にもあげない
I won't give it to anyone
私だけ独り占め
I'll keep you all to myself
だって今までの人と
Because, compared to people until now
同じはいらないんです
I don't need the same thing
ねえもっと give me more love 私のため
Hey, give me more love, for my sake
生きてほしいんです
I want you to live
だからウサギと私は
That's why, like a rabbit and me
寂しくさせないで
Don't make me feel lonely
それじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not being possessive
苦しいのが好き
I like it being painful
ショートケーキ、イチゴみたいに
Like a strawberry on a shortcake
吸ってもいい？
Can I take a bite?
赤く甘い恋だわ
It's a red and sweet love
誰が磨き上げた？
Who polished it up?
「大好き」も
Even my "I love you"
返してもらって全部私に頂戴 もっと
Please return it all and give it to me, more
君は神様が作る
You are, made by God
奇跡のような人
A person like a miracle
つれない顔もその寝顔も
Your cold face and your sleeping face
守ってあげるね
I'll protect them for you
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby I love you is not enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっと give me a kiss more 私は
Hey, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
...full of you
ほどけないリボン結び
An untieable ribbon knot
小指キュって縛って
Tie my pinky tightly
ねえ baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, the first and last
特別にしてね
Please make it special
天、天、天、天、天、天、天
Heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven, heaven
てんてんてんごく、じごじごじごく、オープン・セサミ！
Heaven, heaven, heaven, hell, hell, hell, open sesame!
闇と光の交わるファルセット
Falsetto where darkness and light intersect
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Tasting the psychedelic tonight
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
Zodiac dancing and entangling
恋の駆け引きのタイブレーク
Tiebreak of love's bargaining
飾らない存在ただ気を引きたい
An unadorned existence, just wanting to attract attention
夢見心地触れ合い惑わせたい
Dreaming state, wanting to bewilder with touch
曖昧、解けない、この世界
Vague, unsolvable, this world
悪魔は甘い
The demon is sweet
鮮やかな赤い
A vivid red
愛見つめて限界
Staring at love, reaching the limit
月夜に誘われて
Invited by the moonlit night
天使と
With an angel
悪魔と
And a demon
天使と
With an angel
悪魔と
And a demon
天使と
With an angel
悪魔が今更交差した
An angel and a demon have crossed paths at last
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Or Hell's
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Or Hell's
天国
Heaven
地獄の狭間で出会った
They met in the gap between Heaven and Hell
天使と
With an angel
悪魔と
And a demon
天使と
With an angel
悪魔と
And a demon
天使と
With an angel
悪魔が集って踊れば
If the angel and demon gather and dance
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Or Hell's
天国
Heaven
地獄の門が開く
The gates of Hell will open
闇と光の交わるパナティック
Fanatic where darkness and light intersect
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Tasting the psychedelic tonight
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
Zodiac dancing and intertwining
恋の駆け引きの大ブレイク
The big break in the game of love
Dead Alive
Death! Death! Death!
Bass! Bass! Bass!
生きた魂を獲物において
Placing a living soul as prey
巡る五枚のカード揺れる炎
Five revolving cards, a flickering flame
先にあなたがリリースしたなら
If you are the one to release first
もう迷わないグラスを飲み干して
Don't hesitate anymore, drink up the glass
今夜オールイン降りないこの勝負
All in tonight, I won't back down from this match
今、天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開いていく
Now, the gate connecting Heaven and Hell is opening
天使と悪魔、生者と死者が入り乱れ
Angels and demons, the living and the dead are all mixed together
踊り、笑い、全ては混沌の中に飲み込まれていく
Dancing, laughing, everything is swallowed into chaos
それは世界の終焉であり、新たなる始まりでもあるのだった
It was the end of the world, and also a new beginning
天・天・天・天・天国・天
Hea- Hea- Hea- Hea- Heaven- Hea
天・天・天・天・天国・地獄
Hea- Hea- Hea- Hea- Heaven- Hell
月夜に誘われて
Invited by the moonlit night
恍惚消えない果てない物ない
Ecstasy that won't fade, endless, nothing else
Dance! Dance! Dance!
Iblis dari mana kamu?
Where is this demon from?
Iblis dari mana?
Where is the demon from?
Wah, gatel ya orang iblis, wah wah wah!
Wow, demons are so cheeky, wow wow wow!
Itu, empat tanduk bahaya sekali.
Those four horns are very dangerous.
Iya jadi gini...
So, it's like this...
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I've come from far away...
Iya, jauh-jauh...
Yes, far away...
Apa? Meskipun tidak diundang!
What? Even though I wasn't invited!
Oh, diundang.
Oh, I was invited.
Iya kayaknya kamu undang yang lain tuh tadi.
Yeah, I think you invited others earlier.
Mak- mak- maksudnya...
I- I- I mean...
どういう意味？
What do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba Nihongo?
Why suddenly Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Jepang ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter nggak? Pusing.
Can you stop spinning? I'm dizzy.
Malaikatku pusing guys.
My angel is dizzy, guys.
Iya, aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya.
Yeah, I'm here because I just came to charm you, actually.
Pengen main bareng, pengen godain kamu aja.
I want to play together, just want to tease you.
Sini sini sini sini...
Come here, come here...
Pulang kamu habis ini. Loh? Kamu habis ini pulang sama aku kan?
You're going home after this. Eh? You're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang?
Go home?
Iya, habis ini nggak ada apa-apa lagi kan?
Yes, there's nothing else after this, right?
Ngapain enak-enak aku di atas, masa kamu mau seret aku ke bawah?
Why would I be comfortable up here if you're going to drag me down?
Loh... kita... loh...
Eh... we... eh...
Kita? Kita? Lu aja iblis!
Us? Us? You're the only demon!
Ajak dong, ajak dong, Bang.
Take me along, take me along, Bang.
Kamu saya ajak, aku kesepian.
I'll take you, I'm lonely.
Ayo sini bareng.
Come here, together.
Fallen Angel nih.
A fallen angel here.
Nggak nggak, nggak ada fallen angel.
No, no, there's no fallen angel.
Busur cintanya aku panah.
I'll shoot my bow of love.
Iya iya coba coba coba.
Yeah, yeah, go ahead and try.
Satu, dua, tiga... Poo!
One, two, three... Poo!
How to tame your demon.
Jadi light novel.
Becoming a light novel.
Eh, gimana tadi freestyle kita keren banget ya, guys?
Hey, how was our freestyle? It was so cool, right guys?
Iya, lucu nggak?
Yeah, was it cute?
Atas!
Up!
Bawah!
Down!
Atas!
Up!
Bawah!
Down!
Atas!
Up!
Terus tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
But when you went up, I went down.
Kebalik.
Opposite.
Sengaja! Orang mah kebalik kiri kanan.
On purpose! Usually people do opposite left and right.
Tapi aku beda serta atas.
But I'm different, including up.
Atas!
Up!
Aku bawah.
I'm down.
Atas!
Up!
Kocak, kocak.
Hilarious, hilarious.
Ya udah. Ya udah.
Alright then. Alright then.
Ya udah kalau gitu aku, aku wanita sibuk ya sebenarnya.
Alright then, I'm actually a busy woman.
Jadi kayak nggak, nggak gitu banyak waktu.
So I don't have that much time.
Aku di sini mampir, mampir dikit aja bentaran.
I'm just stopping by for a little bit.
Kasih tiga, kasih lima detik buat kamu.
Giving you three, five seconds.
Busyet! Pemimpin dikit-dikit nih.
Gosh! A leader bit by bit.
Asyik!
Cool!
Oke! Baik!
Okay! Good!
Fiksi ya guys, ini cerita fiksi jangan ditiru adik-adik.
It's fiction, guys. This is a fictional story, don't follow it, kids.
Fiksi, fiksi!
Fiction, fiction!
Fiksi ya guys.
Fiction, guys.
Sensitif ini, sensitif! Fiksi, bohongan.
Sensitive, this is sensitive! Fiction, just a lie.
Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Nggak mau ikut aku lagi?
Don't want to come with me anymore?
Bye bye bye bye bye bye bye!
Jagain nih anak ya guys, kita lihat perilakunya.
Look after this kid, guys. Let's see how she behaves.
Beneran seiso atau nggak, lihat tuh bajunya, jagain jagain.
Is she really pure (seiso) or not? Look at her clothes. Look after her, look after her.
Ya udah, bye!
Alright then, bye!
Bisa jadi Fallen Angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I could become a Fallen Angel because of her instigation, guys.
Awas!
Watch out!
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
A taste of love that'll make you fall for me
なんとかしなくちゃならなくて
I've gotta do something about this
突然メイドになっちゃって
Suddenly, I've become a maid
いつものようにお店の掃除
Cleaning up the shop like always
扉開いちゃって目が合った
The door opened and our eyes met
なんだかキュンとしちゃって
My heart started racing for some reason
慌てん坊にもなっちゃって
And I've become such a scatterbrain
お仕事中に押しに夢中
I'm obsessed with my favorite while working
出口を探しても見当たらないじゃん
I can't even find the exit anymore
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいよ
That's enough
秘密だよね
It's a secret, right?
もういいの
It's okay
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen for you
ねえ、好きって言って
Hey, say you love me
ドキドキキュン送るラブビーム
Doki Doki Kyun, sending you my love beam
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make you fall for me, too
ほらドキドキキュン私大暴走
Look, Doki Doki Kyun, I'm going wild
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
A taste of love that'll make you fall for me
もう君にキュン私大暴走
I'm already Kyun for you, I'm going wild
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make us fall for each other
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in love and let your heart go Kyun
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, this is the taste of love
楽しくて仕方なくたって
Even if I can't help but have fun
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
It's almost time for it to end
会いたくなって落ち込んじゃって
I want to see you so much I'm feeling down
君とぶつかって目が合った
I bumped into you and our eyes met
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
I want to see you again and again
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Today alone just isn't enough
計画通り私の勝利
Just as planned, it's my victory
君に会いたくて仕方ががないよ
I want to see you so much I can't help it
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいの
It's okay
君だけだよ
It's only you
もずっと
Always
愛しあいたいよ
I want to love each other
ねえ、好きって言って
Hey, say you love me
ドキドキキュン君にラブビーム
Doki Doki Kyun, sending a love beam to you
二人夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make us both fall for each other
ほらドキドキキュン私大恋愛
Look, Doki Doki Kyun, my great love
君も夢中にさせる恋のマキ
The roll of love that'll make you fall for me, too
もう君にキュン私大興奮
I'm already Kyun for you, I'm so excited
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make us fall for each other
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in love and let your heart go Kyun
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, this is the taste of love
あわわこのままだったら
Oh no, if it keeps going like this
ここで会うこともなくなって
We won't even see each other here anymore
君の恋が聞きたくなるの
I'll want to hear about your love
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいの
It's okay
秘密なのに
Even though it's a secret
もういいよ
That's enough
このまま好きになってく
I'll keep falling for you like this
ねえ、好きって言って
Hey, say you love me
ドキドキキュン送るラブビーム
Doki Doki Kyun, sending you my love beam
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make you fall for me, too
ほらドキドキキュン私大暴走
Look, Doki Doki Kyun, I'm going wild
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
A taste of love that'll make you fall for me
もう君にキュン私大暴走
I'm already Kyun for you, I'm going wild
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that'll make us fall for each other
だから君がキュンってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in love and let your heart go Kyun
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, this is the taste of love
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hehe, langit sudah mulai gelap, tapi...
Hehe, the sky is starting to get dark, but...
Masih pada semangat nggak semua?
Are you guys still excited?
あー、たくさんのゲストとパフォーマンスしてから、
Ah, after performing with so many guests,
次はコボはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います！
next, Kobo wants to sing alone again!
これから歌うこの曲は、最近コボが気に入ってる曲で、
The song I'm about to sing is one Kobo's liked lately,
聞いたら幸せな気持ちなりました。
and it made me feel happy when I heard it.
皆さんも、この曲聞いて幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you all feel happiness listening to this song too.
それでは次の曲、青山テルマさんの「Happiness」です！
Well then, here is the next song, "Happiness" by Teruma Aoyama!
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, if you're there
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくたって
Even without saying a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I'm feeling it, the one for me
Happiness
Lyrics: 青山テルマ、H.U.B. / Music: 坂詰美紗子
Lyrics: Thelma Aoyama, H.U.B. / Music: Misako Sakazume
落ち込んで眠れなくて
Feeling down and unable to sleep
君との写真見つめている
I'm staring at photos of you
いくつもの笑顔たちに
By so many smiles
助けられるよ my life
I'm being saved, my life
ずっと一緒だよ
We'll always be together
泣いてもいいよ
It's okay to cry
あの涙を抱きしめてくれた
You embraced those tears
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ここにいるから
Because I'm here
すぐに会いたいぜ！
I want to see you right now!
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, if you're there
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくたって
Even without saying a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I'm feeling it, the one for me
君とHappiness どんな時も
Happiness with you, no matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるね please stay by my side
I can walk, please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Since I met you
素直に笑っていられるよ
I've been able to smile honestly
少しずつ自分のこと
Little by little, about myself
好きになった for your love
I've come to like myself for your love
そう今ならね心から
Yes, now from the bottom of my heart
分かり合えるって思えるよ
I feel like we can understand each other
強がらずにありのままで
Without acting tough, just as I am
見つめてくれた
You looked at me
だからHappiness 君のことを
Therefore Happiness, about you
今よりももっと知りたくて
I want to know you more than now
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words
大切なよ the one for me
You're precious, the one for me
私も君に何か
I also want to
できることしたいよ
do something for you
いつでも一緒だから
Because we're always together
守っていけるから
I can protect you
ずっと
Forever
君とHappiness 君がいれば
Happiness with you, if you're there
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくたって
Even without saying a word
感じてるよ the one for me
I'm feeling it, the one for me
君とHappiness どんな時も
Happiness with you, no matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if tears overflow
歩けるね please stay by my side
I can walk, please stay by my side
大切なよ the one for me
You're precious, the one for me
Let's go!
ようこそお越しなさいましたご主人様
Welcome, Master.
お隣座ってせーの
Sit next to me, ready, go!
萌え萌え萌え萌え
Moe, moe, moe, moe
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be happy with this?
目を冷やして笑顔でアップップ
Cool your eyes and smile, Up-pu-pu!
いらっしゃいませとお疲れ様
Welcome and good job.
私とあなたでせーの
You and I, ready, go!
ラブ ラブ ラブ ラブ
Love, love, love, love
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be happy with this?
目を冷やして笑顔でアップップ
Cool your eyes and smile, Up-pu-pu!
ひらりひらり女の子
Fluttering girl
ふわりふわり言葉のソ
Light and fluffy, the seeds of words
それはつまり収めなきゃ
That is to say, must keep it under control
情緒的にある笑顔でアップップ
Emotional smile, Up-pu-pu!
人は見かけによらぬもの
People are not what they seem.
嘘を嘘だと見抜けない
Can't see through lies.
したたかな袖すその顔
A face of a shrewd hem.
ああ鳥肌 寒肌 アップダウン
Oh, goosebumps, cold skin, up and down.
待ち焦がれましたよ いただきます
I've been waiting! Let's eat.
私とあなたでせーの
You and I, ready, go!
ラブ ラブ ラブ ラブ
Love, love, love, love
これはド派手にご苦労様
Thank you for your hard work in style!
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play! Smile and Up-pu-pu!
ひらりひらりここはどこ
Fluttering, where is this?
ふわりふわり外はみぞれ
Softly and lightly, it's sleet outside.
それはつまり収めなきゃ
That is to say, must keep it under control
情緒的にある笑顔でアップップ
Emotional smile, Up-pu-pu!
歌い出す 秘密の鐘
The secret bell starts to sing.
終わることのないこの世界
This world that never ends.
悲しい子供は
The sad child
虚しい子供は
The empty child
眠らせて
Let them sleep.
おままごと 遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Playing house, let's play! Smile and Up-pu-pu!
ひらりひらり女の子
Fluttering girl
ふわりふわり言葉のソ
Light and fluffy, the seeds of words
それはつまり収めなきゃ
That is to say, must keep it under control
情緒的にある笑顔でアップップ
Emotional smile, Up-pu-pu!
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップップ
Let's play! Smile and Up-pu-pu!
アップップ
Up-pu-pu!
Let's dance with me!
何回でもできる True Magic
Can do it any number of times, True Magic.
まだまだ今日は夢見心地
Today I'm still feeling like I'm in a dream.
4時になっても Once Again
Even at 4 o'clock, once again.
何度でも歌って大騒ぎ
Sing as many times as you like and make a fuss.
明日が来るその時まで
Until the moment tomorrow comes,
ねぇ 僕とどうだい？
Hey, how about with me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わりに退屈
Boring at the end of a gloomy week,
そうだけどどうだろう
That's how it is, but what do you think?
誘っていいかな
Can I invite you?
Come on night, Come on night, 構わない
Come on night, Come on night, I don't mind.
どっち向いてる？ こっち向いてる？
Which way are you facing? This way?
あっち向いては 何かじゃなくて
Facing that way is not just anything.
君のことだもん
Because it's about you,
もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ
Listen more carefully.
Hey! 劣勢から逆転
Hey! Turning the tables from a disadvantage.
昨日より今日の方が可愛いし
You're cuter today than yesterday.
居ても立っても居られない
I can't just sit still.
聞こえるゼロ時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight.
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit.
飛び出して 駆け出して
Leap out, run out,
まだまだ夜は終われない
The night is not over yet.
こんな最高の今日日が
This best day today,
明日も続いてくんなら
If it continues tomorrow,
ねぇ 君もどうだい？
Hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでる君の理想の お姫様の席を
The seat of your ideal princess that you've been waiting for...
どうしよう 狙っていいかな
What should I do? Can I aim for it?
Next chance, Let's just aim, 今じゃない？
Next chance, Let's just aim, isn't it now?
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Every Tom, Dick, and Harry to the music,
ステップなんか踏んでみて
Try taking a few steps...
ご機嫌を
Feeling good.
昨日より今日がずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than yesterday.
続けたい時には
When I want to continue,
聞こえるゼロ時告げるチャイム
I hear the chime announcing midnight.
時間切れのその先へ
Beyond the time limit.
終わらない 止まらない
Won't end, won't stop,
まだまだ夜は長いから
Because the night is still long.
こんな最高の今日日が
This best day today...
...ムに
...rhythm,
カラダをあずけてみたら
If you surrender your body,
ほら 魔法みたい
Look, it's like magic!
In my bloom, cuz it's swallows.
騒がしくて馬鹿らしいようなプライド 毎日がいい
I love days with noisy, foolish pride.
魔法なんてありえない でも今だけは現実になるかも
Magic isn't real, but maybe just for now it will become reality.
Oh let's dance
音にのぼって踊れ 君も
Ride the sound and dance, you too!
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法
Special magic in this endless night,
君にも かけてあげるから
I'll cast it on you too.
僕の手をとってよ
So take my hand.
聴こえる鳴り止まないミュージック
The music that won't stop ringing,
魔法が解けるまで
Until the magic wears off.
最高で最強な夜が 今日も更けていく
The best and strongest night deepens again today.
こんな 夢みたいな日々が
If these dream-like days
明日も続いてくなら
Continue tomorrow as well,
ねえ 君はどうだい？
Hey, what about you?
止められないアンコール
Unstoppable encore,
大胆に夜を飾るソング
A song that boldly decorates the night.
何回でもかける魔法
A spell cast over and over,
マジまだ続く夢心地
Seriously, the dreamy feeling still continues.
嘘みたいだけど
It seems like a lie, but
朝が来るその時まで
Until the moment morning comes,
ねえ 僕と踊れ
Hey, dance with me.
うわぁぁぁ！
Uwaaaa!
ここはどこ！？
Where are we!?
わかんにゃい！
I don't know!
え、なんか雲美味しそうじゃなーい？
Eh, don't the clouds look delicious?
食べてみんよー！
Try eating them!
うん、美味しい？
Yeah, are they good?
美味しい！！
They're delicious!!
何をしてるの！？
What are you doing!?
私の雲！！
My clouds!!
食べないで！食べないで！
Don't eat them! Don't eat them!
あ、はじめは食べないでー！
Ah, don't eat them yet!
ああ、私の雲...
Ah, my clouds...
ねえ、誰が食べたの！？
Hey, who ate them!?
Oh calm down! Today's your birthday!
え、誕生日？
Eh, birthday?
誕生日！
Birthday!
Happy birthday!
ありがと。
Thanks.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Welcome welcome!
You must join us, yeah!
コボ先輩と一緒に
Together with Kobo-senpai,
歌って踊りたい？
do you want to sing and dance?
歌って踊りたい！
We want to sing and dance!
Dance and sing yeah!
OK OK OK.
コボの振り付け。
Kobo's choreography.
Kobo no furitsuke? Very nice!
Kobo's choreography? Very nice!
コボ先生と呼んでください。
Please call me Kobo-sensei.
コボ先生！
Kobo-sensei!
あ、ガキ共！
Ah, brats!
ガキ共！？
Brats!?
じゃあ、勉強した？
So, did you study?
もちろん！
Of course!
I studied Kobo-chan senpai's choreography.
じゃあ、行きましょう！
Then, let's go!
行きましょう！ Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
おお、いいね。
Oh, nice.
ポジション OK?
Position OK?
OK! ポジション OK!
OK! Position OK!
OK OK, じゃあ、行きましょう。
OK OK, then let's go.
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Mitsugetsu Un-Deux-Trois
誰もいなくなった
In a town where everyone has gone,
二人だけの街に
leaving only the two of us,
機械仕掛けの時計が
a mechanical clock
夜の訪れ知らせる
announces the arrival of night.
夕闇が空を
The twilight dyes the sky
ワイン色に染めて
the color of wine,
不慣れな二人を
and invites our clumsy selves
舞台へと誘う
onto the stage.
Just a waist, and not a talk,
あなたに魔法をかける
I'll cast a spell on you.
Dusk and waste and half-past ten,
その名前は蜜月
Its name is Honeymoon.
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un-Deux-Trois,
互いの指を絡めて
entwining our fingers together.
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dreams
Chase and whisk and natural tour
あなたに魔法をかける
I'll cast a spell on you
Throw away and over sway
魅惑の蜜 Honey me
Enchanting honey, Honey me
1 2 3 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
1 2 3 un, deux, trois
その唇を重ねて
Press our lips together
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
月明かりが路地裏を
The moonlight illuminates the back alley
黄金色に照らして
Lighting it up in a golden color
おさまる二人は
The two of us settling down
素足のまま踊る
Dancing in our bare feet
1 2 3 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
1 2 3 un, deux, trois
お互いの指を絡めて
Entwining our fingers
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dreams
1 2 3 アン・ドゥ・トロワ
1 2 3 un, deux, trois
その唇を重ねて
Press our lips together
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
うわぁー！
Whoa!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
やったー！
Yay!
Oh my god.
ダンス上手！ダンス上手！
Great dancing! Great dancing!
テリマカシ〜
Terima kasih~
なんか、うん
Like, yeah
スワン
Swan
いや、こぼ先輩もスワン
No, Kobo-senpai is also a swan
スワン。奏でくんもスワン
Swan. Kanade-kun is also a swan
スワン、スワン！
Swan, swan!
ビューティフルスワン
Beautiful swan
めっちゃエレガント
So elegant
エレガントすぎるー！
Way too elegant!
エレガントこぼ先輩！
Elegant Kobo-senpai!
アリガチョウ〜
Arigachou~
難しかった
It was hard
アリガチョウ
Arigachou
いや、簡単ですよ。簡単なのだわ
No, it was easy. It's so simple
簡単だよー！
It's easy!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
来てくれてありがとうね
Thanks for coming
こぼ先輩、呼んでくれてアリガチョウ
Kobo-senpai, thanks for inviting me
ありがとボコボコ先輩アリガチョウ
Thanks Bokoboko-senpai, arigachou
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがとう
Thanks for dancing with us too
テリマカシ〜
Terima kasih~
サマサマ〜
Sama-sama~
サマサマ〜！
Sama-sama~!
ハッピーバースデー！
Happy birthday!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
最後までファイト！
Fight until the end!
ファイトー！
Fight!
じゃ、バイバイ！
Well, bye bye!
みんな行っちゃった...
Everyone's gone...
寂しい...寂しい...
I'm lonely... I'm lonely...
誰も来ないのかな...
I wonder if anyone else is coming...
でも、
But,
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
Let me forget after we say goodbye
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 離さない 戻りたい
Don't leave, I won't let go, I want to go back
Take me free この恋は...
Take me free, this love is...
止まった色味 部屋の中は香水だらけに染めた
Faded hues, the room is stained with the scent of perfume
Jusqu'à l'infini Flavor
Until the infinite flavor
当たり前さえも奇跡
Even the ordinary is a miracle
当たり障りのない君との奇跡
A safe miracle spent with you
どれだけ恋しっても
No matter how much I love you
越えられない君を
I still can't reach you
今ならわかる気がして
I feel like I understand now
今から過去にも戻れるなら
If I could return to the past from here
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
After goodbye, let me forget
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 離さない 戻りたい
Can't leave, won't let go, want to go back
Take me free
愛したい ほど愛しているのよ
I love you as much as I want to love you
気づけばあなたのことばかり浮かべて
Before I know it, I'm only thinking of you
明日になれば大丈夫
Everything will be okay tomorrow
何度言い聞かせればいいの
How many times must I tell myself?
愛という沼に溺れてる
I'm drowning in the swamp of love
私の声は届かない
My voice doesn't reach you
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
After goodbye, let me forget
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 離さない 戻りたい Take me
Can't leave, won't let go, want to go back, take me
サヨナラの前にキスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
サヨナラの後は忘れさせて
After goodbye, let me forget
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear
離れない 離さない 戻れない Take me free
Can't leave, won't let go, can't go back, take me free
変えられない日々 抱きしめたまま
While embracing the days that cannot be changed
closing
Lyrics: 下川美帆, 濱田尚子
Music: 下川美帆
closing
Lyrics: Shimokawa Miho, Hamada Naoko
Music: Shimokawa Miho
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday
弱い心が 捕まる前に
Before my weak heart gets caught
そっと あなたを遠ざけた
I quietly kept you away
ああ こんな気持ち
Ah, this feeling
辛すぎるよ もう
It's too painful now
あなたは誰なの
Who are you?
どこに隠れてたの
Where were you hiding?
ひどく怯えてる
I'm terribly frightened
うつむいたままの
With head held down
見失った私が
I, who lost sight
泣いてた
Was crying
またあの季節
That season again
夜空は白く
The night sky is white
あなたもいて
You were there too
触れてこないで
Don't touch me
嬉しいけど
I'm happy, but...
心が痛い
My heart hurts
離したくない
I don't want to let go
離れたくない
I don't want to leave
でも諦めてた
But I had given up
もうこれ以上 好きになれない
I can't love you any more than this
失う痛み 耐えきれないよ
I can't bear the pain of losing you
変えられない日々 抱きしめたまま
While embracing the days that cannot be changed
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday
ただそばにいて それだけでいい
Just stay by my side, that's enough
素直にはなれないけれど
Though I cannot be true to my feelings
さあ　顔を上げて
Now, lift your head.
歩み始めなきゃ
You have to start moving forward.
リアルな私を　気づいて
Please notice the real me.
またあの季節　この空の下
Once again, in that season, under this sky...
見上げている
...I'm looking up.
傷ついたもの
The things that were hurt...
もう元には
...cannot be returned...
戻らないけれど
...to how they were, but...
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
もう諦めない
I won't give up anymore.
あなたの心
Even if I have to...
傷つけてでも
...hurt your heart...
この気持ちに嘘はつけない
...I can't lie to these feelings.
いつか笑顔で
So that someday...
話せるような
...we can talk with a smile...
私を見つけて
...please find me.
隣にいて
Stay by my side...
聞かせてほしい
...I want you to tell me...
二度と独りにはしないと
...that you'll never leave me alone again.
帰らない日々
While still holding onto...
抱きしめたまま
...the days that won't return...
きっとそうきっと
...surely, yes, surely...
あの日の気持ち受け止めないと
...if I don't accept my feelings from that day...
前に進むことができない
...I won't be able to move forward.
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
一つの願いは
My one wish...
大好きだよと伝えたいだけ
...is just to tell you that I love you.
本当素直じゃないけれど
Even though I'm really not honest with myself.
So... (laughter)
How is it guys?
Then as closing...
Did you take a lot of screenshots?
And ah, how about my new stage?
It's very cloudy here.
Yeah, as you can see, there's two big chill-outs on the left and right.
So cute, right?
みんなどうだった？コボのパフォーマンス。
How was it everyone? Kobo's performance.
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？
Were you able to take a lot of screenshots?
コボの新しいステージはどうだった？可愛いでしょ？
How was Kobo's new stage? It's cute, right?
ビッグチルズがありますので、めっちゃ可愛いよね？
Since there are big Chills, it's super cute, isn't it?
So actually, yeah, we're already at the end of the show, guys.
そろそろお別れの時間になりますよ。
It's almost time to say goodbye.
But don't worry.
Kobo still has something to share with you guys.
まだ皆にお知らせがあります。
I still have an announcement for everyone.
じゃーん！
Ta-da!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 merch set!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set
Birthday Set
Princess!
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time.
And finally, my wish came true!
So, how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the KV is drawn by Scotty-sensei.
Scotty-sensei, arigato!
Scotty-sensei, thank you!
Arigato!
Thank you!
And as you wish, guys...
Finally, ta-da!
Happi Bokoboko Your Kobo
Kobo-ker's Happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobo-kers...
...and perfect for cheering me during events.
Keren banget!
So cool!
Happi, happi, happi. Come on buy, happi, happi.
And if you look closely, this Happi design is like...
...it's like my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's Chillers in the front...
...and me on the back. Right?
And next, we have this...
“Jellyfish Princess on the Wall” Tapestry
..."Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" Tapestry.
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face every morning.
And also don't forget to praise the Lord every day.
Then look at this...
“Jellyfish Princess, you got this” Button Badge Set
...the "Jellyfish Princess, you got this" Button Badge Set.
Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit...
...and the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself.
It looks good, right? Do you like it?
I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag...
...or your hat, or your heart.
Okay, so this one is one of my favorites.
One, two, three... Ta-da! The plushie keychain!
Jellyfish Princess Kobo Plushie Keychain
It's me! But mini Kobo in mini form.
You can bring me anywhere.
On your backpack, your keys, your motorcycle, the car, whatever.
Even next to your computer while you watch my streams.
Soft and squishy.
And finally, we also have the...
Voice Pack / Situational Voice Pack / “Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess”
...Situational Voice Pack.
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
What does it mean? Buy it! Buy it, okay?
Yippee, it's a special voice pack where I talk to you...
...about Jellyfish Princess.
And you know, your one and only just for you.
Set Purchase Bonus / Autographed instant photo-style card
If you buy a set of them...
...you'll get a special bromate with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only.
So you can grab yours from the official shop.
Links are in the description.
So yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo perform today.
以上、こぼ・かなえるのお知らせでした。
That concludes the announcements from Kobo Kanaeru.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので、
I've put the links in the description and chat section,
クリックしてね！
so please check them out!
Oh yeah, but I can hear some of you want an encore.
Encore, encore, encore hoshii?
Encore, encore, do you want an encore?
じゃあ、しょうがないわ。
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Please listen, Sweet Memories.
Sweet Memories
なつかしい 痛みだわ
It's a nostalgic pain
ずっと前に 忘れていた
That I had long ago forgotten
でも あなたを 見たとき
But when I saw you
時間だけ 後戻りしたの
Only time went back
幸せ？と 聞かないで
Don't ask me "Are you happy?"
嘘つくのは 上手じゃない
I'm not good at lying
友達なら いるけれど
I have friends, but...
あんなには 燃え上がれなくて
I can't burn with passion like that
失った 夢だけが
Only the dreams I've lost
美しく 見えるのは なぜかしら
Why is it that they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Even the kindness of the past, now
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Is a sweet memory, sweet memories
キスしたら いけないわ
I mustn't kiss you
傷をひとつ 増やすだけよ
It will only add one more wound
長いあいだ あなたに
For a long time, to you
会いたくて 泣いていたくせに
Even though I was crying because I wanted to see you
あの頃は 若すぎて
Back then, we were too young
いたずらに 傷つけあったふたり
We hurt each other for no reason
色あせた 悲しみも 今は
Even the faded sadness, now
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Is a sweet memory, sweet memories
失った
I've lost
夢だけが
Only the dreams
美しく 見えるのは なぜかしら
Why is it that they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った 優しさも 今は
Even the kindness of the past, now
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Is a sweet memory, sweet memories
フィナーレ
Finale
君は 本当に
You really...
分かってない
...don't understand
フィナーレ
Finale
たとえば Happy End より
For example, more than a Happy End
甘くて豪華なデザートより
More than a sweet and luxurious dessert
君がいいんだよ
It's you that I want
二つの傘より相合傘
More than two umbrellas, sharing one
ちょっと冷たいけど愛するための
It's a bit cold, but if it's the price
代償ならいくらでもどうぞ
To love you, then take as much as you want
ただずっとそばにいたい
I just want to be by your side forever
ねぇ誰を欲しがったって問題ない
Hey, no matter who you want, it's not a problem
二人ぼっちのセカイでずっと
In this world where it's just the two of us, forever
最後の花火を上げて フィナーレを飾って
Light up the final fireworks and decorate the finale
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Fall into a love where miracles fall
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go
味気ないセカイも悪くないね
A tasteless world isn't so bad either
どんなに恋をしたって出会えないよきっと
No matter how much you love, we'll surely never meet again
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our never-ending happiness
いつか今日を忘れても
Even if I forget today one day
君がいいんだよ
It's you that I want
土砂降りの日 愛おしく初めて目が合った
On a day of pouring rain, we lovingly met eyes for the first time
ずっと 覚えておくよ
I'll remember it forever
ねぇ誰を欲しがったって問題ない
Hey, no matter who you want, it's not a problem
二人ぼっちのセカイでずっと
In this world where it's just the two of us, forever
最後の花火を上げて フィナーレを誓って
Light up the final fireworks and vow for the finale
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
Fall into a love where miracles fall
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go
素っ気ないセカイも悪くないね
A cold world isn't so bad either
どんなに恋をしたって忘れられないよきっと
No matter how much you love, I'll surely never forget
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our never-ending happiness
味気ないね
It's tasteless, isn't it?
でもそれがね
But you know, that is
二人の幸せ
Our happiness
Oh my God, I almost cried.
I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys!
Thank you for today!
Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta-senpai because she covered this finale song first...
...and then I was inspired, so yeah.
Aku bolak-balik dengerin ini terus, hehehe.
I kept listening to this over and over, hehehe.
いやいや、今日は来てくれて
No no, thank you for coming today
最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます！
and thank you for watching until the end!
I hope you guys enjoy all the performance...
...um, yeah, this whole stream.
みんな大好き！
I love you all!
Thank you for your birthday wishes.
後で読んであげますね。
I'll read them later.
Bye bye, minna!
Bye bye, everyone!
No more encore! No more encore!
Bye bye!
ボコボコバ、こぼ・かなえる at your service.
Bokoboko ba, Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Bye bye!
Dah-dah!
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
I can't be as bright as now without you! ♡ Kobo ♡